And so, to celebrate the fifth anniversary...
the fifth anniversary...
Um...
...the fifth anniversary of the
founding of the new kingdom...
This is draining.
Excuse me. You called for me?
Oh, Lux, you're here.
I was just practicing for my speech.
Your speech?
I'm giving a speech to the people as
part of the Kingdom Founding Festival.
But I'm not used to such things,
so it's got me a bit down.
I've never really felt that much like a princess to begin with.
Oh! But depending on your answer,
I-I'd have to announce that too.
Huh?
Will you... be my knight?
O-Oh! That!
B-But Lux,
y-you don't need to give me an answer just yet.
Completed activation of this ruin and tuning of the Divine Raiment Machine Dragons, Creator.
At last, the time has come.
Can you begin right away, El Fajula?
Yes, Creator.
The plan is ready to be executed.
Excellent. You're a good puppet.
Can we really trust that girl?
We can. I have her eating
out of the palm of my hand.
She's nothing but a pawn in the game.
Now, let's begin.
Fight for the sky
afuredasu kanjou mou tomaranai
I can't stop the overflowing emotions
mune ni idaitai bokura no gensou
The illusions we hold so dear
Just revolution
kienai aza ni obiete ite mo
Fear of the scar that won't disappear
toki ga mujou ni sugiteku dake
Won't stop the ruthless passage of time
susumeyo aru ga mama
Go forth, the way you are
Let's burst up!
ima koso kawaru toki
Now is the time for change
Let's boost up!
kakumei no kane no ne ga
The sound of the bell of revolution
doko made mo hibiite yuku
Resounds far and wide
To be the soldier
mou koko ni wa irarenai
We can't stay here any longer
To be the soldier
kaze wo kitte yuke ikite yuke
Cut through the wind, live your life
hiryuu no gotoku
Like a flying dragon
hajimari ga michiru mama densetsu ni nare
As the beginning draws near, become a legend
tokihanatte yuke tonde yuke
Release yourself, fly ahead
inochi wo tagirasete
Overflow with life
erabareshi mono wo matsu sekai wa owari da New age
The world that waits for a chosen one is over! New age!
m 720.46 474.09 b 729.28 473.73 737.6 471.61 745.31 475.27 748.15 476.61 750.72 479.77 752.07 482.72 755.1 489.31 754.99 496.45 752.02 503.02 750.68 505.99 748.1 509.1 745.26 510.53 737.6 514.39 729.27 512.3 722.43 512.63 723.41 509.19 724.79 506.36 724.94 503.46 725.29 496.67 725.09 489.85 725.04 483.04 725.01 479.59 726.46 475.42 720.46 474.09 m 732.14 476.18 b 732.14 487.64 732.14 498.78 732.14 509.86 741.7 510.41 746.14 506.72 746.94 497.83 747.22 494.7 747.2 491.5 746.95 488.36 746.22 478.95 742.16 475.56 732.14 476.18 m 560.21 512.25 b 560.78 509.76 561.6 507.57 561.74 505.34 561.98 501.52 562.15 497.63 561.64 493.86 561.37 491.88 559.6 490.09 558.51 488.22 556.5 489.46 552.93 490.52 552.75 491.99 552.04 497.85 552.33 503.84 552.45 509.77 552.46 510.31 553.9 510.81 554.15 512.3 550.68 512.3 547.2 512.3 544.25 512.3 544.84 509.75 545.67 507.42 545.84 505.05 546.1 501.41 546.24 497.68 545.76 494.08 545.49 492.05 543.88 490.21 542.87 488.28 540.73 489.61 536.96 490.72 536.74 492.31 535.97 498 536.34 503.84 536.48 509.62 536.5 510.35 537.73 511.04 538.83 512.2 534.74 512.2 531 512.2 526.96 512.2 531.33 507.98 531.23 492.07 527.1 488.72 533.2 485.28 534.71 485.26 536.46 488.56 544.25 484.02 546.75 484.15 551.72 489.43 552.62 488.71 553.47 487.91 554.44 487.28 561.07 482.93 567.36 485.95 567.79 493.81 568.03 497.96 567.67 502.15 567.93 506.3 568.05 508.2 569.02 510.04 569.7 512.25 566.71 512.25 563.21 512.25 560.21 512.25 m 820.87 513.38 b 816.65 508.82 816.72 507.87 821.33 503.5 820.24 501.5 818.7 499.61 818.14 497.47 816.36 490.74 821.66 485.12 829.5 485.35 833.91 485.48 838.31 485.91 842.71 486.34 843.22 486.39 843.63 487.35 844.52 488.38 842.52 488.74 841.15 488.99 839.73 489.25 839.71 489.5 839.58 489.79 839.66 490.01 843.17 498.68 838.94 505.05 829.65 505.04 828.49 505.04 827.24 504.53 826.19 504.82 824.74 505.23 823.43 506.17 822.06 506.88 823.33 507.67 824.51 508.82 825.89 509.14 827.63 509.54 829.53 509.2 831.36 509.31 833.34 509.43 835.65 509.14 837.23 510.05 839.62 511.42 842.91 513.46 843.25 515.62 843.65 518.11 841.95 521.77 839.96 523.65 835.61 527.76 824.22 528.04 819.04 524.95 814.36 522.16 814.93 517.99 820.87 513.38 m 829.74 513.94 b 828.91 513.94 828.08 513.97 827.25 513.94 823.65 513.78 821.46 515.61 821.05 519.03 820.61 522.71 823.43 523.8 826.33 524.45 827.62 524.73 829.01 524.92 830.29 524.74 834.17 524.2 838.7 523.38 838.64 518.59 838.57 513.49 833.87 514.08 830.24 513.94 830.08 513.93 829.91 513.94 829.74 513.94 m 834.95 496.06 b 835.03 490.76 832.71 487.38 829.31 487.67 825.07 488.05 824.16 491.26 823.98 494.77 823.73 499.51 825.97 502.95 829.35 502.84 834.03 502.68 834.56 499.07 834.95 496.06 m 790.67 513.31 b 786.57 508.88 786.65 507.81 791.3 503.21 787.62 499.18 786.13 494.66 789.34 489.7 791.79 485.9 797.56 484.62 803.43 485.9 805.78 486.41 808.27 486.24 810.7 486.45 811.72 486.54 812.73 486.82 813.74 487 813.72 487.46 813.7 487.92 813.68 488.37 812.35 488.68 811.03 488.99 809.34 489.39 811.3 493.53 812.01 497.84 808.53 501.58 805.11 505.26 800.65 505.29 796.02 504.85 794.76 504.73 793.39 505.84 792.07 506.39 793.29 507.34 794.42 508.91 795.75 509.11 799.51 509.68 803.56 509.05 807.1 510.14 809.53 510.89 812.7 513.51 813.03 515.68 813.41 518.17 811.71 521.82 809.72 523.68 805.33 527.78 793.92 528.04 788.8 524.94 784.27 522.2 784.88 517.99 790.67 513.31 m 799.52 513.94 b 798.69 513.94 797.86 513.97 797.03 513.94 793.45 513.82 790.83 515.74 791.09 519.04 791.25 520.92 793.89 522.86 795.8 524.24 796.84 524.99 798.71 524.91 800.15 524.72 804.02 524.21 808.52 523.37 808.41 518.55 808.31 513.42 803.61 514.11 800.02 513.94 799.85 513.93 799.69 513.94 799.52 513.94 m 793.85 494.61 b 793.88 499.96 795.98 503.03 799.27 502.84 803.9 502.57 804.57 498.97 804.76 495.4 804.99 490.73 802.43 487.33 799.03 487.71 794.48 488.22 793.99 491.74 793.85 494.61 m 582.08 511.24 b 582.7 516.58 583.23 521.15 583.78 525.87 581.48 525.87 577.76 525.87 574.01 525.87 577.9 520.29 577.49 492.04 573.04 488.21 576.54 488.37 579.22 483.53 582.73 487.84 582.88 488.02 584.4 487.08 585.28 486.67 591.74 483.65 598.07 486.05 599.94 492.87 600.92 496.42 601.09 500.5 600.46 504.13 599.17 511.59 593.13 514.8 585.86 512.58 584.96 512.3 584.08 511.95 582.08 511.24 m 582.55 499.65 b 582.55 501.48 581.96 503.6 582.69 505.06 583.74 507.15 585.48 509.76 587.43 510.28 589 510.7 592.82 508.56 593.02 507.19 593.74 502.09 593.79 496.79 593.15 491.69 592.98 490.31 589.14 488.1 587.58 488.52 585.59 489.05 583.74 491.63 582.72 493.76 581.94 495.38 582.56 497.66 582.55 499.65 m 496.36 473.74 b 504.36 473.74 512.36 473.74 520.76 473.74 521.22 476.38 521.69 479.06 522.15 481.74 521.79 482.22 521.42 482.7 521.06 483.18 518.58 475.73 513.58 474.81 507.23 476.57 507.23 481.12 507.23 485.83 507.23 490.48 512.14 492.28 515.27 490.61 516.41 484.76 516.77 485.16 517.12 485.57 517.47 485.98 517.47 490.25 517.47 494.51 517.47 498.78 515.34 494.46 512.41 492.19 507.17 494.36 507.17 499.23 507.17 504.3 507.17 509.95 510.47 509.95 513.88 510.74 516.6 509.72 518.99 508.82 520.61 505.89 522.59 503.85 524.32 510.25 522.62 512.72 516.49 512.73 509.78 512.73 503.07 512.73 497.54 512.73 498.58 509.22 500.02 506.38 500.16 503.47 500.51 496.17 500.29 488.84 500.26 481.51 500.24 478.55 500.91 475.14 495.34 475.27 495.68 474.76 496.02 474.25 496.36 473.74 m 422.13 474.62 b 425.6 473.6 428.4 472.78 431.68 471.81 431.68 477.59 431.68 482.87 431.68 488.97 433.49 487.97 434.64 487.28 435.85 486.68 442.77 483.25 448.32 486.32 448.78 493.96 449 497.78 448.66 501.63 448.91 505.45 449.06 507.65 449.86 509.81 450.44 512.31 447.59 512.31 444.06 512.31 440.56 512.31 444.58 505.48 442.79 498.16 442.08 490.99 441.97 489.96 439.73 488.11 439.13 488.34 436.77 489.24 434.22 490.42 432.6 492.25 430.52 494.59 431.87 509.14 434.23 512.21 430.25 512.21 426.63 512.21 422.9 512.21 427.32 507.37 427.09 478.4 422.13 474.62 m 389.93 473.57 b 400.01 473.57 409.27 473.57 418.76 473.57 419.19 476.72 419.58 479.61 419.98 482.51 419.66 482.83 419.34 483.16 419.02 483.48 416.41 479.45 415.06 473.11 407.76 477.06 407.76 486.88 407.61 497.3 407.95 507.71 407.99 509.09 410.51 510.4 412.28 512.12 406.98 512.12 401.84 512.12 396.69 512.12 401.74 510.73 401.11 506.9 401.09 503.26 401.02 494.33 401.07 485.4 401.07 476.55 396.86 476.04 396.86 476.04 388.8 483.61 389.24 479.7 389.57 476.75 389.93 473.57 m 782.83 513.15 b 780 512.61 777.03 512.05 773.69 511.42 771.49 511.94 768.66 512.99 765.78 513.19 762.13 513.43 758.64 511.64 758.48 507.91 758.37 505.26 760.01 501.8 762.02 500 764.21 498.04 767.81 497.74 770.64 496.38 771.99 495.73 773.89 494.32 773.91 493.23 773.95 491.53 773.01 489.01 771.7 488.3 770.36 487.58 768.06 488.57 766.21 488.94 765.82 489.02 765.61 489.72 765.22 490.01 763.79 491.09 762.34 492.13 760.82 493.06 760.75 493.1 759.4 491.54 759.53 491.36 760.71 489.69 761.87 487.13 763.45 486.79 767.23 485.98 771.31 485.69 775.14 486.21 778.66 486.69 780.11 489.8 780.15 493.33 780.18 497.49 779.94 501.68 780.28 505.81 780.46 507.9 781.66 509.91 782.83 513.15 m 774.57 498.01 b 766.49 500.06 763.29 502.98 764.86 506.82 765.49 508.35 768.41 510.21 769.91 509.92 777.29 508.5 772.82 502.49 774.57 498.01 m 666.73 506.01 b 665.46 511.65 661.02 514 654.35 513.1 647.31 512.16 643.42 506.22 644.08 497.42 644.63 490.15 649.39 485.37 656.14 485.31 662.97 485.26 666.73 489.52 667.61 498.91 662.06 498.91 656.55 498.91 650.96 498.91 650.36 503.61 650.94 507.35 654.5 509.74 659.51 513.1 662.9 508.98 666.73 506.01 m 661.03 496.62 b 661.19 490.32 659.54 487.25 656.09 487.74 651.09 488.44 650.83 492.35 650.81 496.62 654.24 496.62 657.47 496.62 661.03 496.62 m 477.99 499.02 b 472.4 499.02 466.98 499.02 461.32 499.02 460.83 503.82 461.53 507.85 465.67 510.07 470.4 512.6 473.71 509.47 477.34 506.48 477.21 507.24 477.32 508.19 476.91 508.74 473.76 512.99 469.35 513.8 464.46 513.04 459.92 512.33 456.82 509.71 455.61 505.34 453.97 499.36 453.79 493.43 458.49 488.54 461.71 485.19 467.73 484.28 471.93 486.5 476.76 489.04 478.19 493.42 477.99 499.02 m 471.64 496.68 b 471.94 490.88 470.24 487.74 466.89 487.65 463.36 487.55 461.33 490.84 461.4 496.68 464.82 496.68 468.23 496.68 471.64 496.68 m 870.19 499.22 b 864.36 499.22 858.92 499.22 853.3 499.22 853.43 503.96 853.77 508.21 858.26 510.27 862.89 512.39 866 509.34 868.98 505.91 869.24 510.25 865.93 512.92 860.57 513.24 852.27 513.73 847.27 508.98 846.93 500.29 846.58 491.31 851.04 485.61 858.64 485.33 865.77 485.06 869.96 489.84 870.19 499.22 m 853.5 496.55 b 857.22 496.55 860.57 496.55 864.05 496.55 864.06 492.45 864.14 488.57 859.36 487.71 855.94 487.08 853.93 490.25 853.5 496.55 m 682.94 506.42 b 686.41 508.07 689.41 509.94 692.68 510.78 693.73 511.06 696.18 508.88 696.69 507.38 697.08 506.24 695.8 503.92 694.59 502.97 692.14 501.04 688.86 500.07 686.65 497.95 684.95 496.32 683.22 493.32 683.59 491.31 683.96 489.29 686.64 487.15 688.8 486.18 690.91 485.23 693.66 485.61 696.12 485.57 701.23 485.49 701.71 488.63 701.34 491.64 698.46 490.3 695.75 488.7 692.82 487.91 691.9 487.66 689.83 489.38 689.34 490.62 689.01 491.44 690.27 493.42 691.33 494.15 693.9 495.95 697.22 496.86 699.37 499 701.25 500.88 703.3 504.27 702.8 506.41 702.23 508.87 699.27 511.69 696.73 512.55 693.63 513.59 689.83 513.15 686.44 512.64 681.95 511.96 683.32 508.24 682.94 506.42 m 874.19 512.27 b 878.73 507.93 878.58 492.04 874.22 488.63 881.7 485.18 881.99 485.17 883.71 488.52 885.09 487.65 886.48 486.05 887.84 486.06 890.02 486.09 892.29 487 894.28 488 894.67 488.2 894.01 490.5 893.83 491.84 892.72 491.45 891.49 491.25 890.54 490.62 889.8 490.13 889.4 489.1 888.88 488.35 881.92 491.43 880.62 507.34 887.33 512.27 882.65 512.27 878.54 512.27 874.19 512.27 m 620.68 488.34 b 624.08 488.65 627.33 482.82 630.25 488.16 632.25 487.21 634.18 485.57 636.08 485.62 637.77 485.66 639.58 487.39 640.96 488.76 641.32 489.13 640.27 490.91 639.87 492.04 638.55 491.04 637.24 490.04 635.91 489.04 635.65 488.85 635.37 488.68 635.1 488.5 628.54 491.42 627.19 507.39 633.65 512.32 629.11 512.32 625.08 512.32 619.97 512.32 625.52 509.05 623.81 504.34 623.7 500.24 623.59 496.27 625.89 491.42 620.68 488.34 m 604.93 512.21 b 609.59 508.1 609.47 491.94 604.69 488.29 607.77 487.41 610.58 486.6 613.74 485.69 615.81 494.44 612.11 503.78 616.23 512.21 613.41 512.21 609.33 512.21 604.93 512.21 m 674.42 486.49 b 673.95 482.8 673.33 479.11 673.12 475.4 673.08 474.57 674.48 473.65 675.22 472.78 676.05 473.58 677.64 474.42 677.6 475.17 677.38 479.03 676.75 482.87 676.26 486.71 675.64 486.64 675.03 486.56 674.42 486.49 m 610.19 482.84 b 609.31 481.39 607.71 479.92 607.74 478.5 607.78 477.19 609.57 475.92 610.59 474.63 611.87 475.81 613.94 476.83 614.22 478.21 614.49 479.52 612.9 481.22 612.12 482.75 611.48 482.78 610.84 482.81 610.19 482.84
The reason we called you here today
was to ask you about an important matter
that we can't publicly reveal for safety reasons.
And that is?
The Imperial Capital Recapture Operation.
By the looks of it, the former empire's remaining
loyalists have gathered and are planning something.
If recall correctly, their leader's name was Ragreed Forus.
Ragreed Forus!
They are going to execute their plan right after the All Dragons Battle
that will be held during the Kingdom Founding Festival.
They want to strike while our guards
are spread to their thinnest.
So what do you want me to do?
We want you to be our secret weapon against this Imperial Capital Recapture Operation.
According to our spies, in an abandoned village in the northwest of the kingdom,
there are about a hundred Abysses hiding in wait.
A hundred?!
Is that certain?
Yes.
There is little doubt that the Abysses are
being held there by the power of the horn.
We need to take them out
before the rebels make their move.
For that purpose, Lux Arcadia,
we want you to bait out
those hundred Abysses.
Th-This is too much, Prime Minister Nalf!
Not even my brother can
stand alone against that many!
The incident at Ries Island.
If you do this for us, we will turn a blind eye to the transgressions
of your headmistress, Relie Aingram,
and your knight squadron.
I think it's a good deal for you.
How about it?
But...
I accept.
Lux!
We forgot to mention,
but please keep in mind you are to also win the All Dragons Battle.
Win?
Yes.
It's the least we expect to compensate for
the trouble this transgression has caused us.
That's beyond unreasonable!
Airi.
I'll be all right.
You're too softhearted!
I'm sorry, Airi.
Prime Minister Nalf.
I accept both tasks. Baiting out the Abysses
and winning the tournament.
The planning meeting for the Abysses extermination took quite a while.
Are you cold?
Put this on.
No!
Jeez!
Thank you for worrying for me.
But—
Why didn't you tell them
that you can't use Bahamut?
Huh?
You do remember how long you can use Bahamut for, don't you?
Twelve minutes, right?
I know.
Still, someone has to do it.
I'm certain I can find a way.
That's how things always end up.
I thought I could protect you a bit,
if I came along.
Lux?
I'm sorry I always worry you so much.
What's that about?
How would that change anything?
I don't know.
I can't be certain it will help,
but could you do it all the same?
And you want the machine to have the same performance as usual?
Can you do that?
I think I can manage it.
I'm actually pretty good at
such seemingly useless stuff.
That you very much, Miss Lisha.
Don't mention it.
A-Anyway, let's take the victory at the All Dragons Battle tomorrow!
Yes!
Was that her?
I knew it.
Long time no see, Master.
I'm honored to meet you again.
You should be a little more careful.
As the only male survivor of the Arcadia imperial family,
you should keep capable guards.
I'd be more than happy to answer any questions you have for me.
I don't have any intention of fighting you tonight, Master.
Yoruka, last time you said you fight
because of the pact you made, right?
Yes.
Why are you still trying to uphold that pact,
even though the empire is no more?
In order to keep a promise.
To my brother.
Your brother?
Yes.
Since I was a child, I've had a certain talent.
The talent to sense people's killing intent,
and kill then without hesitation.
Huh?
My father called me a "heartless monster".
He died of an illness, so my twin brother inherited the throne at a young age.
Unlike me, he was a sickly child,
but he had a decent human heart.
He protected the kingdom and its people,
and also wanted to protect me,
despite everyone detesting me.
But your kingdom was destroyed by the empire.
Did my father force you into that pact
by taking your brother hostage?
I mean no disrespect, but you, Master,
are much like my brother.
Though your hair and the color of your eyes...
Everything about you looks quite different.
My brother was killed long ago.
Huh?
Then...
I cannot break the pact
I made for my brother.
That's the only way to show
my loyalty to my dead brother.
I intend to destroy this new kingdom
in order to fulfill my pact with your father.
Now, I would like to have your answer, Master.
What are your plans for this kingdom?
I...
Despite all that, I can't go along with your intent.
Because—
It's unfortunate that you and I
have to be enemies, Master.
Please be careful during
tomorrow's All Dragons Battle.
I'd hate to see you die
by someone else's hand.
Everyone, I thank you for your help at Ries Island.
But today, you're here to win for the
new kingdom and for your own sakes.
You got that?
Yes, ma'am!
And so, the two days of the All Dragons Battle began.
The matches on the first day are one-on-one.
Team battles are held on the second day.
In the end, the points each team earns on both days are totaled.
We, the new kingdom's team, lost our first match,
but Celes, Philuffy, and Krulcifer
won the next three.
If my brother and Miss Lisha
win the two remaining matches,
we'd be in the lead at the end of the first day.
Miss Lisha?
How is Tillfur?
She's fine.
Her Machine Dragon is pretty broken down,
but she herself is uninjured.
How is Lux doing?
His opponent is quite a tough one.
But I think it will be over any moment now.
Howling Roar!
Match over!
Contestant judged to be
unable to continue fighting.
Winner: Lux Arcadia.
Another splendid victory
for our Undefeated Weakest.
Was it really?
What?
He has that title because he saves his special techniques for when it really matters,
and just lets time run out in matches such as these.
But this time, he looked like he was in a hurry to win.
It's not like him.
Lux!
Airi!
You didn't have a chance to rest after the match.
Didn't it wear you out?
No. I'm okay.
Thank you.
If I don't manage to get back for the team battle tomorrow, tell the others I wish them luck.
Okay.
All right, Airi, I'm leaving the rest to you.
Come back safely, Lux.
I will.
You're up next, Miss Lisha.
Yes.
I'll ride the momentum we have
and snatch the win!
All right!
Good luck!
Thanks.
I hope everything goes well...
Miss Lisha's match began.
For a while it was an even battle,
and the audience was hyped up.
However, halfway through the battle,
something went wrong.
Did something malfunction?
W-Wait!
I didn't do that!
How?!
Freezing Cannon!
We'd like you to come with us.
Y-You've got it wrong! This wasn't my fault!
We'd like to keep you in custody until the investigation is over,
Your Highness, Princess Lisesharte Atismata.
Hear me out! I did do anything!
You shouldn't argue here.
Regardless of the circumstances, this is not the time and place.
Sharp as ever, I see, fallen prince.
Not only do you not run after being ambushed,
but you immediately strike back.
Are you the one controlling the Abysses here?
I'll have my revenge on you
for beating me on the island.
I made it!
We're a stone's throw from the capital!
Don't let a single one pass!
Mission accomplished.
Good work baiting them out.
The rest is a battle of attrition.
Get some rest for now.
Yes, sir.
I was wondering where Lux was,
in this time of crisis for our princess.
He's baiting out a large group
of Abysses on his own?
Yes.
I'm sorry for not telling you.
That's too reckless!
We should join him!
Please wait!
One of the demands of the kingdom was
to be victorious in the All Dragons Battle.
If you drop out of the tournament, this will have been for nothing.
It's all my fault, isn't it?
He's doing it to make up for what Relie and I did.
I don't think he sees it that way.
Lux wants to protect all of you.
That's his vice.
He always bears everyone else's burdens.
To reduce some of that burden,
while he's fighting,
we should do what we can about
the situation we have at hand here.
You're talking about Lisesharte's case, I assume.
Yes.
There's only one person who could have manipulated Miss Lisha's Machine Dragon.
Yes. The Empire's Dagger, Kirihime Yoruka.
The Divine Raiment of her Yato-no-kami
is manipulation of other Machine Dragons.
We need to find and capture her
to prevent further incidents.
And naturally, to save our princess.
Come to think of it, where did
Saniya disappear to afterwards?
Something's not right.
I feel like we're overlooking something very important.
Hang in there!
What happened?!
It's the rebels.
After the Abysses had worn us out, they attacked us.
But...
The rebel army was supposed to come
after the tournament is over.
Ah, I get it now!
That was their plan all along!
Our main forces have already retreated.
Crossfeed will become the next battlefield.
Did you find anything?
We don't know where she is.
It's almost dawn.
Girls!
Tomorrow's tournament was just canceled due to an emergency.
What is the meaning of that?!
The announcement said that an enemy force
has broken through our defense line
and is advancing toward us
from the northwest.
Lux...
Him?!
We meet again, Lux Arcadia!
The capital will fall.
And then, following the spirit of the former empire,
I'll take the throne as the new emperor.
I pity you.
What?
That large army behind you...
Do you think they're all loyalists of the former empire?
Most of them were definitely sent by a
neighboring kingdom looking to take over Atismata.
Can't you tell you're being used?!
You're a puppet!
A puppet?!
Fine by me.
As emperor, I'll be able to proudly
brandish my power in this kingdom.
I'll be able to do whatever I want with its assets and peasants.
I'll tyrannize to my heart's content.
That's enough for me.
Over my dead body.
You'll never have that!
That's a bold statement from a fallen prince.
What? Not going to use Bahamut on the likes of me?
I'll let you in on a secret then.
An even greater calamity is about to strike at the new kingdom.
A force a Ragnarok can't compare to!
What in the world is that?!
The fifth ruin, The Giant.
What are you going to do now?
What can you do in that sad Wyvern against my army and that giant?!
You do remember how long you can use Bahamut for, don't you?
I'll have to take my chances.
kusaki mo nemuru yoru no sumi de sekai no fushi de
In the nook of night where even trees sleep, in a cranny of the world
neiki ni sotto mimi wo tatete hitomi wo tojiru
I hear the breath of someone asleep nearby,
close my eyes, and prick up my ears
kubisuji ni futto atatakana inochi no tsubu ga
A warm seed of life near my neck
koko ni iru tte sakenderun da koe naki koe de
is screaming that it's there, in a voice without voice
umarekawaretara owarinaki you ni
If we can be reborn endlessly
kimi ga nodo wo itamenakute
Let's take such forms
sumu you na sugata ni narou
that we won't need to scream so hard to be heard
sashiatatte futari tabi doko made arukeru
Now we're traveling, the two of us. How far can we go?
ikeru toko made ikou hohaba awasete
Let's go as far as we can, matching each other's pace
tsukiatatte futari tabi koko made kureba
And when we finally get to the end of the path, the two of us
kigi ni natte tachitsukusou
Let's become trees and stay there
raise ni natte mo zutto koko de nemurou
Even in the next world, let's keep sleeping there
futari nemurou towa ni
The two of us, let's sleep for eternity